A Guide to the Papers of Collins Denny 1872-1943
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Collins Denny Correspondence
  - 1911-1922
    - Asa G. Chandler to Collins Denny 1914 January 12-1921 June 6 (Box-folder 22:9)
    - M. P. Carico to Collins Denny 1920 January 70 1922 February 24 (Box-folder 22:10)
    - M. L. Carlisle to Collins Denny 1914 December 27-1919 April 22 (Box-folder 22:11)
    - H. K. Carroll to Collins Denny 1914 November 30-1922 February 21 (Box-folder 22:12)
    - F. A. Carter to Collins Denny 1918 October 11-1921 October 11 (Box-folder 22:13)
    - Gordon B. Carter to Collins Denny 1911 March 11-1911 July 26 (Box-folder 22:14)
    - J. M. Carter to Collins Denny 1918 December 28-1922 February 16 (Box-folder 22:15)
    - W. W. Cash to Collins Denny 1913 September 22-1914 June 4 (Box-folder 22:16)
    - J. R. Carson to Collins Denny 1911 December 8-1921 August 23 (Box-folder 22:17)
    - W. M. Cassetty, Jr. to Collins Denny 1917 April 14-1922 July 26 (Box-folder 22:18)
    - E. H. Cassidy to Collins Denny 1913 July 16-1920 October 28 (Box-folder 22:19)
    - J. A. Castel to Collins Denny 1912 February 15-1913 September 27 (Box-folder 22:20)
    - A. J. Cauthen to Collins Denny 1914 March 10-1922 May 23 (Box-folder 22:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 22:22 (Box-folder 22:22)
    - J. S. Chadwick to Collins Denny 1913 July 8-1921 April 25 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - E. B. Chappell to Collins Denny 1912 August 21-1922 August 3 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - J. J. Clark to Collins Denny 1919 July 2-1919 December 3 (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ce-Cl 1911-1922 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - S. K. Cockrall to Collins Denny 1914 March 20-1920 February 5 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - P. L. Cobb to Collins Denny 1913 August 27-1921 December 31 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - M. S. Colonna to Collins Denny 1913 January 23-1921 November 10 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Coa-Col 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - G. R. Combs to Collins Denny 1920 February 17-1921 April 21 (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Ed. F. Cook to Collins Denny 1912 September 3-1916 December 18 (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Ed. Cook to Collins Denny 1917 January 3-1922 August 2 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Lawrence Cooper to Collins Denny 1916 May 5-1916 November 30 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - Noah Cooper to Collins Denny 1913 October 3-1938 May 5 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - R. E. Cooper to Collins Denny 1918 October 3-1921 July 19 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - W. A. Cooper to Collins Denny 1912 September 24-1918 April 20 (Box-folder 23:15)
    - W. M. Court to Collins Denny 1912 December 27-1915 July 19 (Box-folder 23:16)
    - R. M. Courtney to Collins Denny 1913 January 14-1922 May 23 (Box-folder 23:17)
    - E. E. Cowan to Collins Denny 1923 March 14-1918 February 13 (Box-folder 23:18)
    - Jackson B. Cox to Collins Denny 1915 January 9-1921 June 17 (Box-folder 23:19)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Com-Coz 1911-1922 (Box-folder 23:20)
    - R. J. Craig to Collins Denny 1912 December 17-1919 February 10 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - W. G. Cram to Collins Denny 1918 September 25-1925 June 29 (Box-folder 24)
    - Bishop Earl Cranston to Collins Denny 1913 January 24-1916 November 28 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - J. B. Craven to Collins Denny 1913 January 10-1937 September 7 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - S. P. Cresap to Collins Denny 1911 February 1-1911 July 7 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - O. B. Crockett to Collins Denny 1918 September 12-1922 January 12 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - G. W. Crutchfield to Collins Denny 1918 August 20-1919 September 1 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Lee G. Crutchfield to Collins Denny 1916 July 14-1921 September 22 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - A. B. Culbertson to Collins Denny 1911 March 10-1912 March 20 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - J. L. Cunningham to Collins Denny 1913 February 15-1914 July 2 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - B. M. Currie to Collins Denny 1919 July 8-1922 May 24 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Cr-Co. 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; C 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Edward T. Dadmun to Collins Denny 1912 August 21-1917 November 10 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Josephus Daniels to Collins Denny 1913 January 17-1931 February 16 (Box-folder 24:15)
    - U. V. W. Darlington to Collins Denny 1913 March 25-1925 December 30 (Box-folder 24:16)
    - U. V. W. Darlington to Collins Denny 1926 January. 4-1940 September 18 (Box-folder 24:17)
    - Arthur K. Davis to Collins Denny 1919 June 14-1922 June 12 (Box-folder 24:18)
    - Charles H. Davis to Collins Denny 1911 December 28-1928 May 7 (Box-folder 24:19)
    - H. G. Davis to Collins Denny 1914 November 22-1916 December 18 (Box-folder 24:20)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Da 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 24:21)
    - C. C. Derrick to Collins Denny 1914 June 23-1922 May 25 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - S. L. Dobbs to Collins Denny 1914 May 25-1918 January 9 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - S. A. Donahoe to Collins Denny 1913 June 12-1917 October 2 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - E. A. Donnelly to Collins Denny 1913 September 23-1918 January 23 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - J. M. Donnelly to Collins Denny 1912 October 24-1918 January 3 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - G. H. Doran to Collins Denny 1914 March 4-1922 July 21 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; De-Dr 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Watson B. Duncan, Jr. to Collins Denny 1914 May 25-1921 October 21 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - W. F. Dunkle to Collins Denny 1911 April 22-1911 June 26 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Du 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - J. H. Eakes to Collins Denny 1918 April 16-1920 April 1 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Robert Echols to Collins Denny 1915 February 8-1920 August 10 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - R. C. Elliott to Collins Denny 1916 May 4- 1918 (Box-folder 25:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ea-El 1911-1922 (Box-folder 25:15)
    - T. J. Eskridge to Collins Denny 1913 May 19-1920 September 10 (Box-folder 25:16)
    - P. C. Eversole to Collins Denny 1918 December 18-1921 September 29 (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Em-Ez 1911-1922 (Box-folder 25:18)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 25:19)
    - W. P. Few to Collins Denny 1912 September 13-1930 July 25 (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Geo. T. Fitzhugh to Collins Denny 1913 March 1-1937 July 13 (Box-folder 25:21)
    - H. R. Fitzgerald to Collins Denny 1913 October 7-1930 December 6 (Box-folder 25:22)
    - J. H. Fitzgerald to Collins Denny 1916 April 25-1918 January 13 (Box-folder 25:23)
    - W. G. Fletcher to Collins Denny 1916 February 3-1925 September 24 (Box-folder 25:24)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Fa-Fl 1911-1922 (Box-folder 25:25)
    - B. F. Fraser to Collins Denny 1912 July 7-1919 February 5 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Douglas S. Freeman to Collins Denny 1916 April 13-1933 November 26 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Geo. D. French to Collins Denny 1913 May 7-1920 November 29 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - R. L. Fultz to Collins Denny 1913 November 14-1930 January 25 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Fo-Fy 1911-1922 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Fa-Gi 1911-1922 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Carter Glass to Collins Denny 1914 December 4-1938 April 27 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - E. M. Glenn to Collins Denny 1915 March 29-1921 November 17 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - J. M. Glenn to Collins Denny 1915 October 18-1937 September 4 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - F. L. Glennan to Collins Denny 1915 January 11-1922 June 10 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - A. H. Godbey to Collins Denny 1912 September 16-1915 March 12 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - T. W. Goodwin to Collins Denny 1917 February 28-1925 July 28 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Gl-Go 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 26:14)
    - John H. Graves to Collins Denny 1914 June 19-1925 November 4 (Box-folder 26:15)
    - James A. Greening to Collins Denny 1912 August 16-1921 October 3 (Box-folder 26:16)
    - C. H. Greer to Collins Denny 1918 August 13-1919 September 10 (Box-folder 26:17)
    - C. C. Gregory to Collins Denny 1921 January 20-1930 March 25 (Box-folder 26:18)
    - R. B. Grider to Collins Denny 1919 October 27-1922 July 19 (Box-folder 26:19)
    - Frank T. Griffith to Collins Denny 1913 March 29-1929 August 28 (Box-folder 26:20)
    - J. L. Griffitts to Collins Denny 1917 May 12-1922 October 14 (Box-folder 26:21)
    - John A. Grose to Collins Denny 1916 February 19-1920 June 21 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Gr-Gy 1911-1922 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Curtis B. Haley to Collins Denny 1920 May 29-1931 September 16 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - John H. Hall to Collins Denny 1912 August 9-1922 October 13 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - W. T. Hamby to Collins Denny 1913 May 20-1916 March 2 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Bishop John W. Hamilton to Collins Denny 1914 June 8-1932 August 9 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ha-Hap 1911-1922 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Smith Hardin to Collins Denny 1915 August 18-1929 October 30 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Charles Hardwicke to Collins Denny 1914 April 29-1920 September 7 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Ira F. Hawkins to Collins Denny 1914 June 28-1930 July 8 (Box-folder 28:1)
    - W. B. Hayes to Collins Denny 1911 August 1-1916 April 12 (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Har-Haz 1911-1922 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Mabel Head to Collins Denny 1915 October 13-1917 May 7 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Mary Hoss Headman to Collins Denny 1913 March 6-1927 July 7 (Box-folder 28:5)
    - W. S. Hendricks to Collins Denny 1920 May 8-1921 January 10 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - C. Henley to Collins Denny 1914 August 14-1930 October 13 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Victor P. Henry to Collins Denny 1918 August 18-1921 September 19 (Box-folder 28:8)
    - W. G. Henry to Collins Denny 1912 May 10-1917 September 24 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Hilary A. Herbert to Collins Denny 1917 April 14-1917 June 14 (Box-folder 28:10)
    - Walter Herbert to Collins Denny 1914 April 170 1931 September 1 (Box-folder 28:11)
    - C. M. Hesser to Collins Denny 1915 October 5-1929 October 31 (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; He 1911-1922 (Box-folder 28:13)
    - John Grier Hibben to Collins Denny 1916 March 13-1917 May 15 (Box-folder 28:14)
    - J. P. Hilburn to Collins Denny 1917 February 17-1917 October 23 (Box-folder 28:15)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Hi 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 28:16)
    - W. E. Hogan to Collins Denny 1913 November 19-1929 April 1 (Box-folder 28:17)
    - Walt Holcomb to Collins Denny 1912 August 27-1927 March 29 (Box-folder 28:18)
    - J. W. Holloway to Collins Denny 1916 March 20-1930 August 23 (Box-folder 28:19)
    - L. A. Holmes to Collins Denny 1915 January 14-1916 August 19 (Box-folder 28:20)
    - R. L. Holroyd to Collins Denny 1914 June 9-1925 May 22 (Box-folder 28:21)
    - Ivan Lee Holt to Collins Denny 1913 March 31-1921 May 23 (Box-folder 28:22)
    - M. H. Holt to Collins Denny 1916 May 12-1918 April 25 (Box-folder 28:23)
    - B. C. Horton to Collins Denny 1913 December 31-1922 February 23 (Box-folder 28:24)
    - Sessler Hoss to Collins Denny 1912 October 18-1919 August 8 (Box-folder 28:25)
    - Harry L. Hout to Collins Denny 1916 September 5-1931 October 10 (Box-folder 28:26)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ho 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - W. A. Humphreys to Collins Denny 1911 January 26-1911 July 31 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - J. G. Huggin to Collins Denny 1914 January 26-1925 November 24 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - A. M. Hughlett to Collins Denny 1914 October 28-1921 February 10 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - T. L. Hulsa to Collins Denny 1918 May 23-1925 February 3 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - G. W. Hummel to Collins Denny 1918 October 1-1937 September 7 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - W. D. Humphrey to Collins Denny 1919 January 29-1921 July 19 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Eppa Hunton to Collins Denny 1912 November 6-1931 December 28 (Box-folder 29:8)
    - D. P. Hurley to Collins Denny 1913 October 11-1924 August 2 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Hu-Hy 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Charles Ireland to Collins Denny 1922 October 7-1925 October 8 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - W. M. Irvine to Collins Denny 1916 June 30-1925 June 5 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - W. T. Irvine to Collins Denny 1913 May 16-1924 September 24 (Box-folder 29:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; I's 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:15)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:16)
    - Nannie R. Jackson to Collins Denny 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:17)
    - Charles C. Jarrell to Collins Denny 1914 February 10-1927 July 28 (Box-folder 29:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ja 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:19)
    - I. C. Jenkins to Collins Denny 1916 December 20-1928 July 23 (Box-folder 29:20)
    - John Jenkins to Collins Denny 1913 May 15-1921 November 22 (Box-folder 29:21)
    - Tom P. Jimison to Collins Denny 1913 August 16-1925 September 7 (Box-folder 29:22)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Je-Ji 1911-1922 (Box-folder 29:23)
    - R. B. John to Collins Denny 1912 December 11-1925 February 14 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - J. W. Johnson to Collins Denny 1914 June 8-1928 April 2 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Luke Johnson to Collins Denny 1913 August 2-1914 October 23 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - J. K. Jolliff to Collins Denny 1913 September 17-1926 January 27 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Bob Jones to Collins Denny 1911 December 12 & 1916 November 14 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - F. B. Jones to Collins Denny 1919 September 25-1922 March 22 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - L. L. Jones to Collins Denny 1911 May 26-1911 August 21 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - W. B. Jones to Collins Denny 1914 July 6-1931 October 6 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - H. H. Jordan to Collins Denny 1922 August 24-1923 July 19 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - Robert F. Jordan to Collins Denny 1919 September 23-1921 January 20 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - James R. Joy Collins Denny 1916 September 21-1941 November 9 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Jo-Jy 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 30:12)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 30:13)
    - C. R. Keiley to Collins Denny 1918 September 19-1921 May 12 (Box-folder 30:14)
    - B. M. Keith to Collins Denny 1915 October 16-1928 December 13 (Box-folder 30:15)
    - B. M. Keith to Collins Denny 1915 October 16-1928 December 13 (Box-folder 30:15)
    - A. E. Kellam to Collins Denny 1917 December 22-1918 November 25 (Box-folder 30:16)
    - Joseph L. Kelly to Collins Denny 1916 March 23-1924 July 21 (Box-folder 30:17)
    - Thos. R. Kendall to Collins Denny 1914 February 3-1917 December 3 (Box-folder 30:18)
    - Hugh E. Kelso to Collins Denny 1919 December 29-1922 January 6 (Box-folder 30:19)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ka-Ke 1911-1922 (Box-folder 30:20)
    - James W. Kilgo to Collins Denny 1913 November 17-1925 September 30 (Box-folder 30:21)
    - P. F. Kilgo to Collins Denny 1914 June 13-1928 July 21 (Box-folder 30:22)
    - W. P. King to Collins Denny 1914 July 6-1937 September 15 (Box-folder 30:23)
    - John F. Kirk to Collins Denny 1921 August 5-1925 September 30 (Box-folder 30:24)
    - W. C. Kirkland to Collins Denny 1914 December 24-1925 April 14 (Box-folder 30:25)
    - C. S. Kirkpatrick to Collins Denny 1922 October 7-1925 May 28 (Box-folder 30:26)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ki-Ky 1911-1922 (Box-folder 30:27)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 30:28)
    - O. C. Laird to Collins Denny 1919 July 30-1920 October 23 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - G. H. Lambeth to Collins Denny 1912 September 28-1921 March 1 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - W. A. Lambeth to Collins Denny 1920 March 15-1941 September 14 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - J. R. Laughton to Collins Denny 1913 November 3-1929 September 3 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - M. E. Lazenby to Collins Denny 1917 November 10-1931 September 16 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; La 1911-1922 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - J. T. Leggett to Collins Denny 1914 July 2-1937 August 30 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - J. D. Lewis to Collins Denny 1918 January 31-1918 April 30 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Lea-Leg 1911-1922 (Box-folder 31:9)
    - D. H. Linebaugh to Collins Denny 1914 March 27-1918 July 16 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - B. F. Lipscomb to Collins Denny 1913 September 19-1928 October 30 (Box-folder 31:11)
    - D. M. Litaker to Collins Denny 1912 November 11-1928 December 5 (Box-folder 31:12)
    - S. D. Long to Collins Denny 1913 April 14-1924 October 10 (Box-folder 31:13)
    - W. P. Lovejoy to Collins Denny 1913 May 13-1914 November 6 (Box-folder 31:14)
    - W. B. Lowry to Collins Denny 1912 January 3-1913 December 3 (Box-folder 31:15)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Li-Ly 1911-1922 (Box-folder 31:16)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 31:17)
    - James E. McCann to Collins Denny 1912 January 31-1918 May 11 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Henry H. McCorkle to Collins Denny 1912 October 11-1921 November 16 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Mrs. R. W. MacDonell to Collins Denny 1916 May 5-1918 January 8 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Letter of W. L. McDowell 1917 November-1918 December 24 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - L. E. McEldowny to Collins Denny 1913 October 29-1917 May 15 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - Charles MacFarland to Collins Denny 1912 November 23-1928 March 23 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - J. G. McGowen to Collins Denny 1920 February 5-1938 February 21 (Box-folder 32:7)
    - The MacMillain Co to Collins Denny 1911 June 9-1926 November 2 (Box-folder 32:8)
    - J. L. McWhorter to Collins Denny 1913 October 7-1921 May 19 (Box-folder 32:9)
    - P. D. Maddin to Collins Denny 1905 August 2-1935 September 9 (Box-folder 32:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ma-Mac 1911-1922 (Box-folder 32:11)
    - J. R. T. Major to Collins Denny 1921 July 18-1937 August 16 (Box-folder 32:12)
    - Jno. Manget to Collins Denny 1938 July 26-1941 October 25 (Box-folder 32:13)
    - L. T. Mann to Collins Denny 1912 October 10-1914 March 19 (Box-folder 32:14)
    - W. H. Mansfield to Collins Denny 1916 May 30-1917 September 13 (Box-folder 32:15)
    - R. Harrison Marks to Collins Denny 1913 July 4-1927 October 18 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - T. F. Marr to Collins Denny 1922 May 20-1925 June 29 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - W. E. Martin to Collins Denny 1913 January 29-1917 December 5 (Box-folder 33:3)
    - W. A. Massebeau to Collins Denny 1914 May 29-1916 May 20 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - W. T. Mathis to Collins Denny 1918 August 27-1922 January 17 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - C. W. Mathison to Collins Denny 1916 July 27-1916 October 31 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - L. K. May to Collins Denny 1918 October 18-1922 May 9 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Wm. J. Maybee to Collins Denny 1914 May 30-1928 June 11 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ma 1911-1922 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - R. A. Meek to Collins Denny 1914 January 2-1938 May 5 (Box-folder 33:10)
    - S. E. Mercer to Collins Denny 1915 March 12-1928 November 24 (Box-folder 33:11)
    - Daniel Merritt to Collins Denny 1913 August 20-1929 January 8 (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Me 1911-1922 (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mi 1911-1922 (Box-folder 33:14)
    - R. A. Moody to Collins Denny 1916 July 20-1917 December 29 (Box-folder 33:15)
    - Mary Moore to Collins Denny 1913 February 18-1916 April 18 (Box-folder 33:16)
    - R. E. L. Morgan to Collins Denny 1912 February 16-1928 June 29 (Box-folder 33:17)
    - James C. Morris to Collins Denny 1905 January 6-1916 May 3 (Box-folder 33:18)
    - W. E. Morris to Collins Denny 1913 December 11-1937 September 17 (Box-folder 33:19)
    - H. C. Morrison to Collins Denny 1910 May 28-1939 September 6 (Box-folder 33:20)
    - E. D. Mouzon to Collins Denny 1910 March 6-1922 November 28 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - E. D. Mouzon to Collins Denny 1923 January 6-1933 November 10 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mo 1911-1922 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ma-My 1911-1922 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - W. A. Newell to Collins Denny 1912 October 23-1925 June 19 (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - J. H. Nicholson to Collins Denny 1918 January 18-1938 March 3 (Box-folder 34:7)
    - Thos. J. Norsworthy to Collins Denny 1911 March 2-1912 April 20 (Box-folder 34:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Na-Ny 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 34:10)
    - T. C. O'dell to Collins Denny 1913 November 4-1932 February 4 (Box-folder 34:11)
    - W. R. Odell to Collins Denny 1912 November 26-1941 June 18 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - W. B. Oliver to Collins Denny 1917 April 13-1917 August 16 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - John Orr to Collins Denny 1913 May 13-1916 January 15 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - W. C. Owen to Collins Denny 1916 March 21-1925 December 29 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Z. Paris to Collins Denny 1912 September 18-1931 October 26 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Firzgerald Parker to Collins Denny 1913 January 10-1927 May 6 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Sir Gilbert Parker to Collins Denny 1914 December 28-1917 January 10 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - R. O. Payne to Collins Denny 1913 September 9-1929 September 18 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Pa 1911-1922 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - W. W. Peele to Collins Denny 1922 June 2-1927 January 1 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - C. C. Perkins to Collins Denny 1912 October 10-1929 August 2 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - J. W. Perry to Collins Denny 1912 October 10-1929 August 2 (Box-folder 35:14)
    - C. H. Phillips to Collins Denny 1920 July 4-1920 August 27 (Box-folder 35:15)
    - D. A. Phillips to Collins Denny 1914 June 12-1926 June 4 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - W. L. Pierce to Collins Denny 1913 August 6-1925 March 13 (Box-folder 35:17)
    - W. W. Pinson to Collins Denny 1912 June 21-1925 October 7 (Box-folder 35:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Pe-Pi 1911-1922 (Box-folder 35:19)
    - R. B. Platt to Collins Denny 1913 September 9-1932 March 30 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - M. T. Plyer to Collins Denny 1912 August 8-1926 January 25 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - F. S. Politt to Collins Denny 1916 April 5-1928 September 5 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - T. N. Potts to Collins Denny 1912 December 20-1921 December 7 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Paul S. Powell to Collins Denny 1918 December 13-1925 August 13 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - J. B. Preston to Collins Denny 1918 June 28-1925 April 14 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Bishop Clare Purcell to Collins Denny 1916 June 27-1940 September 9 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - J. W. Quillian to Collins Denny 1913 June 24-1920 March 15 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Q n.d. (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - J. W. Rader to Collins Denny 1918 May 29-1921 December 8 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - W. M. Rader to Collins Denny 1911 January 3-1912 February 28 (Box-folder 36:14)
    - T. C. Ragsdale to Collins Denny 1912 September 28-1926 September 15 (Box-folder 36:15)
    - E. H. Rawlings to Collins Denny 1915 August 25-1937 November 30 (Box-folder 36:16)
    - C. L. Read to Collins Denny 1912 October 11-1927 July 28 (Box-folder 36:17)